Guide to the COLLECTION NAME HERE, YYYY-YYYY IBT0086
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Teamsters for a Democratic Union materials
1969-2002
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT0086
3 record cartons Photocopies of articles and other documents relating Teamsters for a Democratic Union plus copies of Convoy Dispatch.
This collection contains materials pertaining to the Teamsters for a Democratic Union (TDU), its predecessors, and connected organizations.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
This collection is divided into four series: Teamsters for a Democratic Union Files, Convoy Dispatch Newsletters, Labor Notes Newsletters, and Union Democracy Review Newsletters. Each series is arranged chronologically.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
CHOOSE ONE:
Gift of [Name], [Date] [(Accession Number)]
Transferred by [Office or Department Name], [Date] [(Accession Number)]
Purchased by Gelman Library, [Date] [(Accession Number)]
Loaned by [Name], [Date] [(Accession Number)]
Biographical / Historical
According to the Teamsters for a Democratic Union, "Teamsters for a Democratic Union is a grassroots organization of thousands of members across North America, working together to rebuild Teamster Power. For more than 30 years, TDU has been uniting Teamsters to put our union to work for the members."
Teamsters for a Democratic Union was founded by rank-and-file Teamsters in 1976 amidst growing concern about the role of organized crime in the union and lack of proper focus on rank-and-file members. In 1979, TDU and the Professional Driver's Council (PROD) merged to create a single Teamsters reform group. Throughout the 1980's, TDU fought for better contracts and advocated for the end of corruption within the higher ranks of the union.
In 1991, TDU-endorsed reform candidate Ron Carey was elected general president of the union. Throughout the Carey presidency, multiple major reforms were made to reduce corruption in Teamster leadership. After his reelection in 1996, the IBT Election Officer ordered a re-do. Carey was disqualified and James P. Hoffa won the presidency.
Since the 1990's, the TDU has fought to protect pension plans, build rank-and-file power, and hold elected officials accountable.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains paper materials pertaining to the Teamsters for a Democratic Union (TDU) and its partner organizations. Materials include newsletters (series 2, 3, and 4) as well as TDU convention files, pamphlets, book excerpts, and studies. This collection contains both files in favor of and against TDU.
General
- Teamsters for a Democratic Union Files, 1969-2006
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains records and scanned articles relating to the TDU and other affiliated Teamsters groups ranging from 1969 to 2006.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Friedman- TDU Democracy, ND (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - TDU Funding (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Foundations (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Teammate / Overdrive Magazine, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - TDU and IBT in the 1970's (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Analysis of TDU, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - TDU- Origins of Political Struggle, ND (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - PROD Patches and Decals (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - TDU Decals, ND (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - FASH- Rank and File Rebellion in the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - RAFT, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Fighting to Win- IS, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Root and Branch- Keep on Trucking, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - TDU Articles, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - PROD Manifesto, ND (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - TDU - IBT Convention, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - TDU Founding Convention, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Local 776 TDU Flyers and Articles, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - TDU New York Times Magazine Article, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - TDU Rank and File / Restless Articles, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - TDU / International Socialists Members, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Radical America Dissent in the International Brotherhood of Teamsters by Rinaldi, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Desparate Bargain TDU Chapter, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - TDU Convention, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - TDU Articles, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - TDU Bylaws, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Local 776, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - TDU Convention, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - PROD and TDU Merger, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - TDU by S. Lynd, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - TDU Carhaulers, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - TDU Local 776, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Freight, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Carhaul, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Getting the Most from the Grievance Procedure, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Local 776 Trainess NMFA, Deaner, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - TDU Organizing for a Better Contract, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - TDU Members Bulletin, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - From the Horse's Mouth, W. Pa. TDU Newspaper, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - TDU Local 776, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Local 776, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - TDU Convention, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Who Runs the Teamsters Report, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - TDU Convention, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Roy Williams's Bid for the Marble Palace, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - TDU New Directions, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Steering Committee, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Who Rules the Teamsters, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Organizing in UPS, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Teamster Rank and File by Friedman, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - TDU UPS, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Rebel Teamsters by Hoyt, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - TDU Convention, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Where is the Teamster Rebellion Going?, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - "Blast" Articles, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Local 435, Linda Gregg, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Associated Press Teamsters Right to Vote Article, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - TDU/Freight, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - UPS Contract, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - TDU Convention, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - IBT Convention, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - TDU Constitution, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Casual Road Pay, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - TRF Finances, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - How to Recruit TDU Members, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - TDU Order Form, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Gregg, Linda (Local 435), 1986 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - TDU/UPS, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - C. Pa. TDU Membership, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - TDU RICO Lawsuit, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - TRF Finances, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - TDU Convention, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - ISC/TDU, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - TDU Ranks Try to Save the Teamsters, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Jackie Presser Response to an Editorial by Ken Paff, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - ECTDU Membership Applications, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Freight, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - TDU Correspondence, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - TDU / McCarthy, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - TDU Grocery News, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - TDU Membership Newsletter, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - TDU Carhaul, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - TDU Convention, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - TDU ISC, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - TDU ISC, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - TRF Finances, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - An Injury to One...by Moody, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Democracy in TDU, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - TDU/ISC, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - C. Pa. TDU Membership, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - TDU Convention, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - TDU/ISC, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - TDU/ISC, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - TDU/UPS, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - TRF Friends Newsletter, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - TDU Wives Newsletter, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Lehigh Valley TDU, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - TDU Welcome Letter, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Local 773 Delegate Election to Nominate Ron Carey, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - TDU ISC Minutes, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - TDU ISC Minutes, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - TDU/UPS, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - TRF Finances, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Olson Kudla, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Committee to Elect Ron Carey, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - TDU Critique, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - TDU Organizing Chapters, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Reform Officers Network, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - TDU Convention, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Ron Carey Election Articles and Correspondence, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Lehigh Valley, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - TDU Convention, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - TDU/UPS, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - TDU Chapters, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Reforming the Teamsters Article, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - TDU/UPS Strike, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - TDU/Freight Contract, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - TDU Convention, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Dollars and Sense Labor Issue, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Trade Union Politics by Brenner, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - TDU Convention, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - TDU Seattle, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Hoffa Watch, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - TDU Activist, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - TDU Convention, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - IBT Pensions, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - IBT Convention, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - IBT Convention/Election, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - TDU Membership Bulletin, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - TDU 25th IBT Convention, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - TDU Activist, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - Jimmy Hoffa Junior: Corruption by Bohner, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Hoffa Junior: His Record of Ties to Employers by Bohner, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - TDU Activist, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - Transformation of US Labor Unions Book Chapter- TDU, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Savvy Troublemaking by Carroll, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - TDU Convention, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - TDU/UPS Contract, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - Fight at UPS by Labotz, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - Hoffa Watch, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 140)
  - TDU Flyers, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - Tom Leedham Slate, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - TDU Articles, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - TDU Articles, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bureaucracy is Best for Unions by Moody, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - IBP Strike, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - TDU Financial Reports, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - TDU Convention, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - TDU Convention, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - TDU Mailing List, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - TDU UPS, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - TDU Elections, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Adelante, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - TDU Articles, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - TDU Articles, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Local 763, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - TDU Convention, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - TDU Election, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Savvy Troublemaking by Caroll, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - TDU Election, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - TDU Articles, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - TDU Convention, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - TDU Consent Decree, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Matty Moroum, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Convoy Bundle Rates, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - TDU UPS Contract, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Local 961 Elections, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Local 938, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Dues Increase, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Left Criticism, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - TDU Fundraising Letter, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - TDU Articles, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - TDU Convention, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Ins and Outs of Managing a Local Union, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Joe Fahey, Local 912, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Maria Martinez, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - 12 Ways to Measure Hoffa's Success, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - TDCC Convention, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Bob Hasegawa Local 174, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - TDU Articles, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - TDU Articles, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - TDU Convention, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Local 556, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Local 556, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Local 556, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - TDU Articles, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Teamster Reformer- Goldberg, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - TDU Convention, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - TDU Convention, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - TDU Convention, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Local 200, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - TDU Articles, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Local 604, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Local 805, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Rebuilding Labor Movement at the Grassroots, ND (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - TDU Suggested Readings, ND (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - TDU Leadership Training, ND (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - IBT Leadership Lifestyles, ND (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - IBT Analysis, ND (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Conspiracy in the Trucking Industry Article (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Literature List, ND (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Bumper Stickers, ND (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Spying on your Employer Article, ND (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - TDU Building Chapters, ND (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - TDU Membership Application, ND (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Central States Pension, ND (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Organizing Teamsters, ND (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - TDU Grocery Industry (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - What Has TDU Done, ND (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Local 229, ND (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Local 776 LaRouche, ND (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - TDU Patch and Pins (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Convoy Dispatch Newspaper, 1972-2002
  This series contains PROD newsletters from the late 1970's and Convoy Dispatch newsletters ranging from the 1970's to the early 2000's.
  - PROD Newsletter, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - PROD Newsletter, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - PROD Newsletter, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - PROD Newsletter, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - PROD Newsletter, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - PROD Newsletter, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - PROD Newsletter, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Convoy Dispatch, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 122)
- Labor Notes Newsletter, 1979-2002
  This series contains Labor Notes newsletters ranging from the late 1970's to the early 2000's.
  - Labor Notes, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Labor Notes, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Labor Notes, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Labor Notes, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Labor Notes, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Labor Notes, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Labor Notes, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Labor Notes, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Labor Notes, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Labor Notes, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Labor Notes, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Labor Notes, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Labor Notes, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Labor Notes, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Labor Notes, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Labor Notes, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Labor Notes, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Labor Notes, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Labor Notes, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Labor Notes, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Labor Notes, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Labor Notes, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Labor Notes, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Labor Notes, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Labor Notes, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Labor Notes, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Labor Notes, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Labor Notes, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Labor Notes, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Labor Notes, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Labor Notes, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Labor Notes, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Labor Notes, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Labor Notes, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Labor Notes, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Labor Notes, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Labor Notes, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Labor Notes, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Labor Notes, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Labor Notes, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Labor Notes, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Labor Notes, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Labor Notes, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Labor Notes, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Labor Notes, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Labor Notes, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Labor Notes, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Labor Notes, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Labor Notes, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Labor Notes, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Labor Notes, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Labor Notes, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Labor Notes, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Labor Notes, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Labor Notes, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Labor Notes, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Labor Notes, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Labor Notes, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Labor Notes, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Labor Notes, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Labor Notes, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Labor Notes, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Labor Notes, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Labor Notes, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Labor Notes, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Labor Notes, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Labor Notes, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Labor Notes, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Labor Notes, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Labor Notes, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Labor Notes, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Labor Notes, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Labor Notes, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Labor Notes, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Labor Notes, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Labor Notes, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 76)
- Union Democracy Review Newsletter, 1985-2002
  This series contains Union Democracy Review newsletters ranging from the mid 1980's to the early 2000's. Union Democracy Review was published by the Association for Union Democracy.
  - Union Democracy Review, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Union Democracy Review, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Union Democracy Review, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Union Democracy Review, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Union Democracy Review, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Union Democracy Review, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Union Democracy Review, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Union Democracy Review, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Union Democracy Review, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Union Democracy Review, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Union Democracy Review, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Union Democracy Review, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Union Democracy Review, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Union Democracy Review, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Union Democracy Review, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Union Democracy Review, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Union Democracy Review, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Union Democracy Review, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 96)